PAUL LEWIS: This is "Supercharged."
这是“增压”。
It's the show where I take the sites that you've submitted.
这是我浏览的程序
And I go through them.
您提供的网站。
And I look for performance issues.
并寻找其性能问题。
Paul Lewis, voice of an angel, face of a pig.
保罗·刘易斯（Paul Lewis），天使般的声音和猪脸。
Last time, we looked at "The Guardian's" page
在上一集中，我们研究了页面加载性能
load performance.
“卫报”
This time we're going to do pretty similar.
我们今天要做的事情非常相似。
It's going to be "The Guardian" because we're going
将成为“卫报”，因为我们
to wring it for all it's worth.
我们将充分利用它。
Why wouldn't you?
为什么不呢
A little bit of something to clarify from last time.
从上次澄清以来的小订单。
I showed my bookmarklet, which is really cool,
我提供了非常酷的书签，
to toggle the styles on and off and switch off
要关闭并打开样式并关闭
the remote styles and just leave the inline styles that
遥远的模式和离开内心的模式
were shipped with the page.
与页面一起发送。
There was a bug in the bookmarklet, which
该工具存在问题
is why it was causing some of that page content
导致某些页面内容
to go a bit crazy.
表现异常。
Who writes code with bugs?
谁编写的代码有错误？
Not me.
我不是他们
We've updated the source code.
告诉我们源代码。
So if you want it, you can grab it yourself.
如果您愿意，可以自己使用。
What I'm going to do is I'm going
我要做的是
to look, this time, at the scrolling performance.
我看，应用程序中的滚动性能。
And I'm going to do that on mobile.
我将在移动设备上进行操作。
Because if you've got performance issues
因为如果遇到性能问题
on a mobile device you're really going to feel it.
在您的手机上，您将已经感受到。
You're really going to notice.
您会真正注意到它。
And so it's a really good opportunity
所以这是一个很好的机会
to just step in and go, well, if I can fix it on mobile,
要加入并加入，如果我可以在手机上修复它，
it's going to be amazing and blazing fast on desktop.
它在计算机上将具有很高的速度。
So it's a really good opportunity.
因此，这确实是一个巨大的机会。
So I have my trusty Nexus device here.
好吧，我有一个值得信赖的Nexus设备。
And what I'm going to do is I'm going to unlock it, first
我先解锁
of all, for it is locked.
因为它是锁定的。
I wear a lot of hats in this show.
在这个节目中，我戴着很多帽子。
In my job, I wear a lot of hats.
在我的职业中，我戴着很多帽子。
This one is jazz hat.
这顶爵士帽。
I'm going to go across to Chrome Inspect.
我要检查Chrome。
And you can see here that it's showing me that Chrome Dev is
在这里您可以看到它显示了Chrome Dev
available, which is good.
是的，那很好。
And there's a new tab.
这是一个新标签。
Ready to rumble?
准备战斗了吗？
Ready to-- what?
-什么？
Got to put my teeth back in.
我必须回牙。
(IMITATING OLD MAN) Ready to rumble.
准备战斗。
Grab that.
等一下
Let's go Open tab with URL.
让我们打开一个带有URL的标签。
And click on that.
然后我们按一下。
And open it.
并打开它。
And that means we can also inspect it, which
这意味着我们可以检查它，
brings up Chrome's Dev tools.
这带来了Chrome Dev工具。
Urban Paul.
保罗文明。
I'm street.
我是黑帮老大
I can be down with the kids, you see.
我可以照顾孩子。
I am-- I'm cool like you.
我和你一样很棒。
And I am on the Timeline, which is my personal favorite place,
我按时到了，这是我最喜欢的地方，
apart from, well, maybe the Elements or the console.
除了项目或控制台。
I just like-- I like them all so much.
我只是爱-我非常爱他们。
It's like choosing a favorite child.
这就像选择您喜欢的孩子。
I can't do it.
我做不到
I'm going to do scrolling performance.
我将检查滚动性能。
Because scrolling's an animation.
因为滚动是图形。
And if there's a problem with scrolling,
如果有滚动问题，
it's going to really kind of be the most obvious thing
这肯定会很清楚
to the users of the site.
对于本网站的用户。
And you know, this is a content site.
而且您知道该网站的内容。
So scrolling should be 60 frames a second
因此滚动应为60 fps。
and that kind of thing.
这样的事情。
So combo hat, urban jazz.
组合帽子和文明的爵士乐。
And I will record.
我会记录。
And I'm going to scroll like that.
我会这样通过。
And every time the frame rate drops during that scroll,
在滚动过程中，每当帧频下降时，
there's a bright yellow block, which is the JavaScript.
有一个亮黄色的组，JavaScript。
And so, you know, it's good to know that it's JavaScript.
因此，很高兴知道它是JavaScript。
But I think we want a little bit more detail.
但我认为我们需要更多细节。
So what I'll do is I'll switch on the JavaScript profiler.
所以我要做的是运行探查器JavaScript。
OK, so we have the JavaScript profiler switched on.
好，探查器JavaScript已打开。
Going to hit Record.
我将按注册。
I'm just going to do a bit of a scroll.
我将做一些滚动。
Most of the time, I rely on editing
大多数时候我依靠编辑
to sort the wheat from the chaff.
从大麦中分离出小麦。
Yeah?
是啊
Wheat being the one thing in every 100
小麦是100内的一件事
that I say that's worth listening to.
告诉他值得一听。
Most of the time it's like, (WITH HIGH-PITCHED VOICE)
在大多数情况下，
I don't like mung beans.
我不喜欢金cow豆。
So Timeline.
这样的时间表。
Time line.
时间表。
When you look at timelines, it's often really good
当您查看时间表时，通常会很好
to try and break down the work.
尝试量身定制工作。
And one of the things that the JavaScript profiler will do
JavaScript要做的一件事是探查器
is it's going to color code the results based on the file.
是它按文件为结果着色。
So if you see the same color, you
因此，如果您看到相同的颜色，
know it's coming from the same file.
我知道这是同一文件。
And that's actually extremely useful when you're
这真的非常有用
starting to kind of divide and say,
我们首先分开说，
well, where is the work coming from?
好吧，工作来自哪里？
You know, what's responsible for the work?
谁负责这项工作？
So you can see, I think most of these, lazy load, load slot,
所以您可以看到，我认为其中大多数是缓慢加载，加载广告位
there's a message JS.
有一条JS消息。
I'm not sure what that is.
我不确定这是什么。
But my hunch is that they're trying to show a message.
但是我的活动告诉我，他们正在尝试显示消息。
But it's going through Raven.js, which that's an error catcher.
但是它通过捕获器Raven.js传递。
So I guess that's just acting as a bit of a gateway.
因此，我认为这可以作为网关。
Pub ads impl.
pub广告的Impl展示。
So there is something to do with ads here.
因此，有一些与广告有关的东西。
Move along to the next one.
转到下一个。
Another animation frame.
另一个动画帧。
More ads, Evaluate Script.
更多广告，评估脚本。
There's an ads there.
这里有一个广告。
Let's have a look.
让我们来看看。
A ready state change.
更改就绪状态。
So there's something going on where there's presumably
所以某些事情本应存在的地方发生
some Ajax in.
一些Ajax。
And we've got some Parse HTML here.
我们这里有一些Parse HTML。
So that implies that there's something
那意味着它存在
that's being lazy loaded in.
疯狂地持有某种东西。
But that's causing a massive recalc style,
但是这种重新计算模式会导致大量重新计算。
which is pretty intense, actually,
实际上，这是很多重点
like 117 milliseconds.
大约117毫秒。
And again, this is all locking up the main thread.
同样，所有这些都锁定了主线程。
I actually went through the timeline.
您实际上传递了时间表。
And I think this is a really good exercise for everyone
我认为这对每个人都是很好的练习
to do, is go through a timeline recording.
这是流量记录时间表。
And start marking out exactly what's going on.
并开始教授到底发生了什么。
So in this case, there's Outbrains, some visitor
因此，在这种情况下，存在Outbrains，一些访客正在跟踪。
There's some ads stuff.
关于广告，有些事情。
"The Guardian" itself is doing a bit of set
“卫报”本身没什么用
up over multiple request animation frames.
建立多个动画帧请求
There's a whole block here that's
这里有一整块
just garbage collection, collecting the garbage,
只有废物的收集，废物的收集，
taking the trash out.
扔垃圾。
I say trash.
使用浪费一词。
In England, it's rubbish.
在英格兰，他们说垃圾这个词。
But one of the interesting ones is this recalc style.
但是有趣的是这种重新计算风格。
You can see that it's recalculating the style
您可以看到它重新计算了模式
and then triggering a layout.
然后开始布局。
Forcing a recalc style, triggering a layout.
强制重新计算模式开始布局。
And this is a really bad state for us to be in.
对我们来说，这是非常糟糕的情况。
However, it is third-party code and so
但是，它是第三方代码，因此
there's only so much that you can do.
我们无能为力。
I think the thing to remember is that when
我想要记住的是
you're running third-party code, it's
当您运行第三方代码时，
running alongside your code.
它在您的代码旁边起作用。
And everybody's got contention for the main thread,
每个人都在争夺主线，
that one thread that everybody's on.
每个人都在使用的线程。
And so it's a bit like that time I
就是这样
had 10 people in a five-person tent.
当我在五个人的帐篷里有10个人时。
That was just awkward.
真是尴尬。
So there we go.
所以我们到了。
I think the majority of the issues that they're facing
我认为他们面对的大部分事情
are to do with scrolling performance and the fact
附加到滚动性能和事实，
that this code is not running at a time that's
这段代码一次不起作用
convenient for the browser or for the user, really.
不适合浏览器和用户。
You know, web performance has never just
网络性能从未如此
been about page load.
只需加载页面。
It's also about things like animations
也与图形有关
and about responding to user taps and things like that.
关于响应用户标签和类似内容。
So I'd take a look at that.
所以我想看看。
I'd see if there's a way to just defer that a little bit more
我想看看是否有办法再改变一点
to when the user isn't interacting.
直到用户处于非活动状态。
Don't forget, you can subscribe.
别忘了，您可以注册。
You should do that.
一定要
Do it.
做这个。
Done it?
你做到了吗？
Well done.
干得好
Well done, you clicked it.
干得好，我按了一下。
And you can submit your sites, also.
您也可以提交您的位置。
A good thing to do.
很好做。
And I will take a look at them.
我会看看它们。
And I will catch you next time.
下集再见。
Yes!
是的
Come on!
加油！
Throw a dart, they said.
他们告诉我扔一支箭
It'll be easy, they said.
这很容易。
You ready?
准备好了吗
Miles off.
数英里远。
Next time.
下一次